it gives a feel to it to interact with
your magnets or we can do aluminium and
magnetize it we've done that way back to
95 and everything else we had a whole
table aluminium table the whole damn
thing is violently magnetic
right but it's very easily discharged
people's bodies can discharge it very
easily if they've got the wrong feels in
them we had a whole table magnetic
attractive and everyone lock any damn
thing on this strong this guy walked in
there and he goes just letting the table
and she's gone
gold and everything else non-magnetic
attractive mirror so how now when they
had these um
metal detectors
okay they set up this field and there
you go some metal detection and it would
pick up
you know anything magnet
so aren't they doing now
everything else from these did you just
switch the switch
there's a guy's got those a heap of
those um what's your name
those uh
future
washing machines he's having to play
with him all right
yeah these are made of pizzas oh okay
yeah
we'll replace them from a mechanical
point of view another is a washing
machine no it pulls it pulls all the way
down here don't use it with the washing
machine
what you're doing with the magnets
nothing yet
you find out what you can do and they've
already got that mounts more back out
than they ever put in so he's playing
with electric motors too
no he's having to play okay
so
just fossil running
there's a lot of people mucking around
in there
anyway
so
within what i'll take up and show you
now before sort of peter comes back here
because really don't
i really don't want too many people
seeing and knowing who will put the
stuff up when i don't want to you know
to send it well
people to see what i do and everything
else and i'm not hiding i'm not trying
to do it away from you but i just do it
but i don't want everybody else to know
where i'm from because i've got no
reason to put it out there and i also do
not want everybody chasing me up anyway
okay and see what i do and one know how
and then you get the to say you
know you're full of then the other
father say oh yeah i can believe that
but show us
have you witnessed the actual um
uh
you know the what peter had on the tapes
here on the my wife's vp commodore with
her spa
yeah with you
the spark everywhere here we've seen
that yeah
but there's no reason for it
okay
it doesn't shut down spark it doesn't
shut down people it doesn't play the
computer doesn't block diets it doesn't
do anything shuts apart here i'll get a
cell there jack
in there you got to see what uh
joseph
yeah
you didn't get one of me
another joey
it's different it's also pulling
insulators to pieces and stuffing up
nice
different yep
this is called
a p cell or a
peter melbourne
i'm peter
if this is a peter cell and peter says
okay tell peter to prove it to you
that's okay by running something
well that's what he's using on the front
of this is he running anything
i don't know the way you do
no because my name's joe and his name's
peter and i don't do this and i can see
and feel these things you've got
different kinds of stainless you've got
you've got three different kinds of
stainless in there how do you know
i don't know if you're going to have it
analyzed and i'll pretty much believe
you but i can see i can feel i can sense
who
i don't know
if i look at it and everything that's
look this one don't go all the way from
the script what do you think where do
you think that big black mark down there
comes from well that's the theme that's
the it's not the same that's not the
same
but where do you think he's got all
these other marks there's a seam there i
put the hana through it it did not the
hana would go sideways that's straight
up and down long ways and it's going
right through these other cells look
look on the outside yeah well what is it
it's a field effect around the well
because that world it changed the
stainless and then when you put a field
into this and everything else it changes
it all the way through shuts it down all
the way across so it'll never work not
that with that with those depends on
what you want
you want to play
do you want to make bubbles yeah well
then you tried to light the buttons yeah
what do they do
not much oh well they just hold it
no they're not because they go yellow
flame no that's oxygen oh is it that's
all a couple of times when i added some
electrolyte and stuff you got the white
bubbles and they really they really
cracked i like the implosion it was i
thought did your ears ring like oh yeah
what this one was death for half the
night
right you never got that electrolyte but
then it died off you know they just died
because the water started to warm up and
electrolyte was fading out and you
didn't get anything charging up you got
everything discharging
so the electrolyte and your water and
everything else all went the wrong
direction
once you actually release first and
everything else was a negatively charged
oxygen instead of all oxygen is
positively charged and what what did
that was a negative charge hydrogen
so it's very hard to get them off
electrolyte one get them off
well i was using um
phosphoric acid
that's turned around and it's eating all
the the um chromium out of there
okay that's powdering up
that's what it's battering up and it's
um it's eating it
and what you got in there is insulated
because you can see the insulators
and they're dead shorting underneath the
plates so it's not neutral plates in
there you've got active plates all the
way because that thing in there is dead
shorting all those plates out and what
you've got now is a positive and the
negative but i can't even see the
the um the negative side of it because
there's no clean
anywhere and you would say the outside
is positive
okay
but to me that's the only point at the
present moment which is negative
because every one of those plates on
each side sure
are corroded and corrosion and is going
to what you might call positives there's
no part in their negative
okay now
let's look at it as such do we want a
negative ideally on a positive phil
they're called neutral plates
neutral is not positive but not negative
which means it will not break down and
it will not cause anything to go to it
and if you had anything on a plate and
everything else it would actually polish
it up
it would clean it okay so he's not even
good grade stainless that's actually
probably a
that's a rum off a um
steamer
thing on the side
he even knew what it was yeah there was
actually copper rolled around it you
know i can tell them
these insulators
aren't through you see yeah barking
through but you're pulling everything to
piece and doing the same as that
okay
all these
you pull them out now look that's a
table there's no positive and negative
on there and you started pulling not
just the chromium out of that one you
have a look as copper and everything
else that you pulled out there look at
the coloring and you got this hot yeah i
did you
is
he jumped to conclusions too fast so
it's okay to have the magnetics down the
seams and all that no
uh
so you've got to line it up look at all
the seams
seal them look at all the arcing how
much foliage did you put into this 24
that's okay you shouldn't still do that
but that's a flame and burn up i've
probably on 24 with a bit of uh
okay
i now found something
i found a standard battery
i found positive oxide where there look
at it
where's the negative
in there
so you're not looking for the opposite
here you're looking for it in there
no